  export const games =   [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20was%20the%20first%20Call%20of%20Duty%20title%20released%3F",
"correct_answer": "October%2029%2C%202003",
"incorrect_answers": [
"December%201%2C%202003",
"November%2014%2C%202002",
"July%2018%2C%202004"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20code%20name%20given%20to%20Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%204%20during%20its%20development%3F",
"correct_answer": "Project%20Needlemouse",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Project%20Bluespike",
"Project%20Roboegg",
"Project%20Darksphere"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20virus%20that%20infected%20New%20York%20in%20Tom%20Clancy%27s%20The%20Division%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dollar%20Flu",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ebola",
"Red%20Poison",
"Smallpox"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20the%20following%20titles%20by%20Valve%20is%20not%20based%20on%20a%20Community%20Mod%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ricochet",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Day%20of%20Defeat",
"Counter-Strike",
"Alien%20Swarm"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20map%20featured%20in%20Arma%203%20named%20%22Altis%22%20is%20based%20off%20of%20what%20Greek%20island%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lemnos",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ithaca",
"Naxos",
"Anafi"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20world%27s%20first%20video%20game%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tennis%20for%20Two",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Spacewar%21",
"Pong",
"Space%20Travel"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20Gamecube%20Version%20of%20%22Resident%20Evil%22%20what%20text%20document%20is%20open%20on%20the%20monitor%20of%20the%20computer%20in%20the%20Visual%20Data%20Room%3F",
"correct_answer": "A%20GDC%20Document",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Text%20Document%20on%20Herbs",
"Nothing",
"Document%20on%20B.O.Ws"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20Animal%20Crossing%20series%2C%20which%20flower%20is%20erroneously%20called%20the%20%22Jacob%27s%20Ladder%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lily%20of%20the%20Valley",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hydrangea",
"Harebell",
"Yarrow"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20long%20are%20all%20the%20cutscenes%20from%20Metal%20Gear%20Solid%204%20%28PS3%2C%202008%29%20combined%3F",
"correct_answer": "8%20hours",
"incorrect_answers": [
"4%20hours",
"12%20hours",
"5%20hours"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20online%20games%20was%20originally%20named%20LindenWorld%20in%20it%27s%20early%20development%3F",
"correct_answer": "SecondLife",
"incorrect_answers": [
"ActiveWorlds",
"IMVU",
"HabboHotel"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20game%20was%20exclusive%20to%20Dreamcast%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pen%20Pen%20TriIcelon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sylvester%20%26%20Tweety%20in%20Cagey%20Capers",
"Perfect%20Dark",
"Tetrisphere"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20main%20character%20in%20the%20video%20game%20VA-11%20HALL-A%3A%20Cyberpunk%20Bartender%20Action%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jill",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Dana",
"Alma",
"Anna"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20souls%20game%20was%20not%20directed%20by%20Hidetaka%20Miyazaki%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dark%20Souls%202",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Demon%20Souls",
"Dark%20Souls",
"Dark%20Souls%203"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Before%20Super%20Smash%20Bros.%20contained%20Nintendo%20characters%2C%20what%20was%20it%20known%20as%20internally%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dragon%20King%3A%20The%20Fighting%20Game",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Contest%20of%20Champions",
"Smash%20and%20Pummel",
"Fighter%20of%20the%20Ages%3A%20Conquest"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20long%20was%20the%20World%20Record%20Speed%20Run%20of%20Valve%20Software%27s%20%22Half-Life%22%20that%20was%20done%20in%202014.",
"correct_answer": "20%20Minutes%2C%2041%20Seconds",
"incorrect_answers": [
"45%20Minutes%2C%2032%20Seconds",
"5%20Minutes%2C%2050%20Seconds",
"12%20Minutes%2C%2059%20Seconds"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20Fallout%20series%2C%20on%20which%20date%20did%20The%20Great%20War%20happen%3F",
"correct_answer": "October%2023rd%2C%202077",
"incorrect_answers": [
"May%2015th%2C%202058",
"December%2014th%2C%202069",
"November%205th%2C%202076"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20weapon%20classes%20DO%20NOT%20appear%20in%20the%20first%20Monster%20Hunter%20game%3F",
"correct_answer": "Bow%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hammer",
"Heavy%20Bowgun",
"Light%20Bowgun"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20Monster%20Hunter%20Generations%2C%20which%20of%20these%20hunter%20arts%20are%20exclusive%20to%20the%20Longsword%3F",
"correct_answer": "Unhinged%20Spirit",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Shoryugeki",
"Provoke",
"Demon%20Riot"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20Counter%20Strike%3A%20Global%20Offensive%2C%20what%20is%20the%20code%20implanted%20onto%20the%20C4%20as%20the%20Terrorists%20plant%20the%20bomb%3F",
"correct_answer": "7355608",
"incorrect_answers": [
"7890728",
"7256380",
"7726354"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20Animal%20Crossing%3A%20New%20Leaf%2C%20which%20of%20these%20paintings%20from%20Redd%27s%20Art%20Gallery%20is%20always%20genuine%3F",
"correct_answer": "Warm%20Painting",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jolly%20Painting",
"Neutral%20Painting",
"Wistful%20Painting"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20Pok%C3%A9mon%20cannot%20learn%20Surf%3F",
"correct_answer": "Arbok",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Linoone",
"Tauros",
"Nidoking"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20game%20created%20by%20Masahiro%20Sakurai%20and%20Satoru%20Iwata%20that%20would%20eventually%20evolve%20into%20%22Super%20Smash%20Bros.%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dragon%20King%3A%20The%20Fighting%20Game",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nintendo%20Legends%3A%20Fight%21",
"Martial%20Arts%3A%20King%20of%20the%20Hill",
"Aerial%20Warriors%3A%20Supreme%20Battle"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20title%20of%20the%20game%20%22Luigi%27s%20Mansion%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20only%20letter%20to%20not%20appear%20with%20a%20pair%20of%20eyes%20in%20it%3F",
"correct_answer": "s",
"incorrect_answers": [
"n",
"i",
"m"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20do%20the%20video%20games%20No%20Man%E2%80%99s%20Sky%20and%20Mighty%20No.%209%20have%20in%20common%3F",
"correct_answer": "Both%20were%20announced%20in%202013.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Both%20were%20crowdfunded.",
"Both%20were%20developed%20by%20indie%20studios.",
"Both%20were%20released%20for%20the%20PlayStation%203."
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20Super%20Smash%20Bros.%20for%20Nintendo%203DS%20and%20Nintendo%20Wii%20U%2C%20who%20was%20the%20sixth%20fighter%20to%20be%20added%20to%20the%20game%20post-launch%3F",
"correct_answer": "Corrin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cloud",
"Bayonnetta",
"Ryu"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20trophies%20are%20there%20in%20%22Super%20Smash%20Bros.%20for%20Nintendo%203DS%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "685",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1360",
"716",
"1155"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "During%20development%20of%20%22Super%20Mario%20World%22%2C%20Yoshi%27s%20hard%20saddle%20was%20originally%20which%20of%20these%3F",
"correct_answer": "A%20shell",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20slide%20of%20Gelatin",
"A%20poffin",
"A%20spike"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20original%20DOOM%20%281993%29%20which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20cheat%20code%3F",
"correct_answer": "IDCLIP",
"incorrect_answers": [
"IDFA",
"IDDQD",
"IDSPISPOPD"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20games%20in%20the%20The%20Legend%20of%20Zelda%20franchise%20was%20released%20in%20North%20America%20before%20Japan%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Legend%20of%20Zelda%3A%20Twilight%20Princess",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Zelda%20II%3A%20The%20Adventure%20of%20Link",
"The%20Legend%20of%20Zelda%3A%20Four%20Swords%20Adventures",
"The%20Legend%20of%20Zelda%3A%20Majora%27s%20Mask"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20variant%20of%20the%20MP5%20is%20depicted%20in%20Counter-Strike%201.6%3F",
"correct_answer": "MP5N",
"incorrect_answers": [
"MP5SD",
"MP5K",
"MP5RAS"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20Zombies%20mode%20of%20%22Call%20of%20Duty%3A%20Black%20Ops%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20%22Pack-A-Punched%22%20version%20of%20the%20%22Galil%22%20called%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lamentation",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Galvanized%20Atomic%20Lead%20Insertion%20Liquidator",
"Gabig",
"Predictive%20Death%20Wish"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20%22The%20Binding%20of%20Isaac%22%2C%20which%20item%20instantly%20kills%20Mom%20and%20Mom%27s%20Heart%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Bible",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Halo",
"Brimstone",
"Book%20of%20Shadows"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20monster%20in%20%22Monster%20Hunter%20Tri%22%20was%20causing%20earthquakes%20in%20Moga%20Village%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ceadeus",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Alatreon",
"Rathalos",
"Lagiacrus"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "According%20to%20the%20lore%20of%20%22Starbound%22%2C%20what%20does%20the%20%22Colony%20Deed%22%20do%20when%20it%20is%20placed%20down%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sends%20out%20an%20advertisement%20for%20someone%20to%20move%20in.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Teleports%20somebody%20from%20somewhere%20on%20the%20planet%20it%20is%20placed.",
"Teleports%20a%20random%20person%20to%20the%20location.",
"Materializes%20a%20new%20being%20at%20it%27s%20location."
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20%22Call%20Of%20Duty%3A%20Zombies%22%2C%20which%20map%27s%20opening%20cutscene%20shows%20%22Richtofen%22%20killing%20another%20version%20of%20himself%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Giant",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Shadows%20Of%20Evil",
"Der%20Eisendrache",
"Moon"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20%22Call%20Of%20Duty%3A%20Zombies%22%20map%20%22Origins%22%2C%20where%20is%20%22Stamin-Up%22%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Generator%205",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Generator%203",
"Generator%204",
"Excavation%20Site"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20characters%20wasn%27t%20a%20villian%20in%20Club%20Penguin%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Director",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Herbert%20P.%20Bear",
"Tusk",
"Ultimate%20Proto-Bot%2010000"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20was%20the%20Valve%20Corporation%20founded%3F",
"correct_answer": "August%2024%2C%201996",
"incorrect_answers": [
"December%2026%2C%201994",
"March%2022%2C%201997",
"March%2013%2C%201997"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%27s%20original%20human%20girlfriend%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madonna",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Celeste",
"Sierra",
"Nina"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20which%20game%20did%20the%20character%20%22Mario%22%20make%20his%20first%20appearance%3F",
"correct_answer": "Donkey%20Kong",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Super%20Mario%20Bros.",
"Super%20Mario%20Land",
"Mario%20Bros."
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20gaming%20series%20includes%20%22The%20Diabolical%20Box%22%20and%20%22The%20Curious%20Village%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Professor%20Layton",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Persona",
"Etrian%20Odyssey",
"Sam%20%26%20Max"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20plane%20of%20existence%20in%20MicroProse%27s%201997%20%22Magic%20the%20Gathering%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shandalar",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Theros",
"Ravnica",
"Amonkhet"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20vault%20in%20the%20video%20game%20%22Fallout%203%22%20is%20the%20home%20of%20multiple%20clones%20named%20Gary%3F",
"correct_answer": "Vault%20108",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Vault%20101",
"Vault%2087",
"Vault%2021"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20%22Pikmin%22%20games%2C%20which%20of%20the%20following%20pikmin%20colors%20lacks%20it%27s%20own%20%22Onion%22%20nest%3F",
"correct_answer": "Purple",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Winged",
"Blue",
"Rock"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20creation%20of%20the%20%20Entertainment%20Software%20Ratings%20Board%20%28ESRB%29%20is%20often%20associated%20with%20Mortal%20Kombat%20and%20what%20FMV%20video%20game%3F",
"correct_answer": "Night%20Trap",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sewer%20Shark",
"The%20Daedalus%20Encounter",
"Corpse%20Killer"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20indie%20farming%20game%20%22Stardew%20Valley%22%2C%20which%20NPC%20hates%20the%20%22prismatic%20shard%22%20item%20when%20received%20as%20a%20gift%3F",
"correct_answer": "Haley",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Abigail%20",
"Elliott",
"Lewis"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%202004%2C%20which%20person%28s%29%20created%20%22Roblox%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "David%20Baszucki%20and%20Erik%20Cassel",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Erik%20Cassel",
"Jonas%20Alto%20and%20Sarah%20Smith",
"James%20Kolein"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20the%20game%20Warframe%2C%20what%20Mastery%20Rank%20do%20you%20need%20to%20have%20to%20build%20the%20Tigris%20Prime%3F",
"correct_answer": "13",
"incorrect_answers": [
"6",
"18",
"10"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20was%20Pokemon%20GO%20released%20in%20North%20America%3F",
"correct_answer": "July%206th%2C%202016",
"incorrect_answers": [
"June%205th%2C%202016",
"May%2024th%2C%202016",
"January%202nd%2C%202017"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "GoldenEye%20007%20on%20the%20Nintendo%2064%20was%20planned%20to%20allow%20you%20to%20play%20as%20all%20previous%20Bond%20actors%2C%20with%20the%20exception%20of%20who%3F",
"correct_answer": "George%20Lazenby",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Roger%20Moore",
"Sean%20Connery",
"Timothy%20Dalton"
]
}
]